ILGWU. Collective Bargaining Agreements, 5780/075
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Agreements. United Popular Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1944 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Agreements. Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc., 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Agreements. Atlantic Apparel Contractors' Association, Inc., 1985-1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Agreements. Associated Corset and Brassiere Manufacturers, Inc., 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Agreements. Cleveland Joint Board, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Agreements. Cloak, Dress Drivers' and Helpers' Union, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Agreements. Fashion Apparel Manufacturers' Association [folder 1 of 2], 1978-2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Agreements. Fashion Apparel Manufacturers' Association [folder 2 of 2], 1978-2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Agreements. Greater Blouse, Skirt and Neckwear Contractors' Association, Inc., 1967-1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Agreements. ILGWU Dressmakers' Joint Council, 1973-1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Agreements. Joint Board of Coat, Suit and Allied Garment Workers' Unions, 1973-1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Agreements. Knitted Outerwear Manufacturers' Association [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Agreements. Knitted Outerwear Manufacturers' Association [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Agreements. Ladies' Apparel Contractors' Association, Inc., 1979-1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Agreements. New York Coat, Suit, Dress, Rainwear and Allied Workers' Union, 1988-1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Agreements. Northeast, Western Pennsylvania and Ohio Department (ILGWU), 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Agreements. Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1978-1985 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Agreements. Snowsuits, Skiwear, Leggings, Infants' and Novelty Sportswear Union, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Agreements. Waterproof Garment Workers' Union, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 18)